Member Pricing Free Until 2025

Meet Micro Center Member Pricing

Unlock savings on the products you love with Member Pricing today!

Completely free until 2025

No credit card needed to join

Sign in with your verified account to qualify

Even more savings on top of already great deals

Savings automatically applied during checkout

Returns are always free and you can save time by starting returns online

Look for the green tag throughout the site to unlock more Member Pricing!

Already have a Micro Center account? You automatically qualify for member pricing for free until 2025! Just sign in to see the price

We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website. You can view our [Privacy Policy](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx) and information regarding our use of cookies [here for more information about cookies](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx). Accept Accept Privacy Policy and Terms

Site Selections: Account Login, Store Selection, Cart Information

Product Search Form

Search for product    

* 
    
    Dallas
    
    Open until 9PM

* Open 9am - 9pm today
* * Close Your Store Modal
    * Your Store
        
        Dallas
        
    * TX - Dallas

    * 13929 N Central Expy
        
        Dallas, TX 75243
        
        Questions? Text or call
        
        Open Now
        
        Mon 9 to 9, Tue 9 to 6, Wed - Sat 9 to 9, Sun 10 to 7
        
        [Directions
        
        to
        
        Dallas](https://maps.google.com/maps?daddr=13929+N+Central+Expy+Dallas%2c+TX+75243)
        
        [Dallas

        Store Info](https://www.microcenter.com/site/stores/dallas.aspx "Store Info")

    * Store Locator:
        
        Store Lookup Zip Code 
        
        * Brooklyn
            
            850 3rd Ave Brooklyn, NY 11232
            
            9.2 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Brooklyn
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=115)
            
        * North Jersey
            
            263 McLean Blvd Route 20 Retail Center Paterson, NJ 07504
            
            10.3 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            North Jersey
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=075)
            
        * Flushing
            
            71-43 Kissena Blvd Queens, NY 11367
            
            11.1 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Flushing
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=145)
            
        * Yonkers
            
            750-A Central Park Ave Yonkers, NY 10704
            
            12.2 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Yonkers
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=105)
            
        * Westbury
            
            655 Merrick Ave Westbury, NY 11590
            
            22.4 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Westbury
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=171)
            
        * St. Davids
            
            550 E Lancaster Ave Ste C St Davids, PA 19087
            
            88.5 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            St. Davids
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=061)
            
        * Parkville
            
            1957 E Joppa Rd Parkville, MD 21234
            
            165.2 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Parkville
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=125)
            
        * Cambridge
            
            730 Memorial Dr Cambridge, MA 02139
            
            184.8 mi
            
            [Shop
            
            Cambridge
            
             Store](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx?storeID=121)

* * [
        
        Hello, Sign in
        
        Account & Lists
        
        ](https://account.microcenter.com/auth/signin?RedirectUrl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.microcenter.com%2fsite%2fcustomer-support%2fprivacy_policy.aspx)
        
        Close Your Account Modal
        
        Account Options

* My **Cart:**
* [
    
    Cart& List](https://cart.microcenter.com/ "View My Cart")

Product category, brand navigation and general site naviation

    X Close the product navigation menu
    
    * Top Deals
        
        Top Deals options - 6 groups of items - 24 total selections
        
        * PC Parts
            
        * Computers
            
        * Peripherals
            
        * Electronics
            
        * Networking
            
        * Explore All Categories

    * PC Parts
        
        PC Parts options - 10 groups of items - 51 total selections
        
        * Processors/CPUs
            
        * Motherboards
            
        * Computer Memory
            
        * Graphics Cards & Accessories
            
        * Drives & Storage
            
        * Cases & Accessories
            
        * Air & Water Cooling
            
        * Expansion Cards
            
        * Laptop Parts
            
        * Explore More

        Try our [Custom PC Builder](https://www.microcenter.com/site/content/custom-pc-builder.aspx)
        
    * PC Builders
        
        PC Builders options - 3 groups of items - 9 total selections
        
        * Build a Custom PC
            
        * Streaming & Gaming
            
        * Showcase

    * Computers
        
        Computers options - 7 groups of items - 46 total selections
        
        * Laptops & Tablets
            
        * Desktops
            
        * Computer Monitors
            
        * Portable Accessories
            
        * Peripherals
            
        * Business Solutions
            
        * Explore All Categories

    * Apple
        
        Apple options - 7 groups of items - 22 total selections
        
        * Mac
            
        * iPad
            
        * Hardware & Accessories
            
        * Audio
            
        * Apple Watch
            
        * Apple iPhones
            
        * Explore All Categories

        Savings on [Apple Laptops](https://www.microcenter.com/search/search_results.aspx?N=4294967288+4294820432)
        
    * Electronics
        
        Electronics options - 13 groups of items - 73 total selections
        
        * Televisions
            
        * Monitors
            
        * Photography & Imaging
            
        * Printers & Scanners
            
        * Cell Phones & Accessories
            
        * Portable Electronics
            
        * Home Theater
            
        * Flash Memory & Card Readers
            
        * Security & Home Automation
            
        * Headphones, Speakers & Microphones
            
        * Maker/STEM
            
        * Webcams & Video Capture
            
        * Explore All Categories

    * Maker/STEM
        
        Maker/STEM options - 5 groups of items - 19 total selections
        
        * 3D Printing
            
        * Boards & Projects
            
        * Electronics
            
        * DIY Arcade Cabinets & Retro Gaming
            
        * Quadcopters & Drones

    * 3D Printing
        
        3D Printing options - 2 groups of items - 6 total selections
        
        * 3D Printing
            
        * Accessories

    * Networking
        
        Networking options - 6 groups of items - 27 total selections
        
        * Wireless Networking
            
        * Wired Networking
            
        * Servers & NAS
            
        * Networking Accessories
            
        * Modems
            
        * Explore More

        Save on [Wireless Routers](https://www.microcenter.com/category/4294966869/Wireless-Routers)
        
    * Accessories
        
        Accessories options - 10 groups of items - 50 total selections
        
        * Cables & Switchboxes
            
        * Keyboards, Mice & Tablets
            
        * Carrying Cases
            
        * Power & Protection
            
        * CD/DVD/Blu-ray Media
            
        * Ink & Toner
            
        * Office & Home
            
        * Cable Management
            
        * Refreshments & Gadgets
            
        * Explore All Categories

        Shop all [Mice](https://www.microcenter.com/category/4294966892/Mice-and-Trackballs)
        
    * Gaming & Software
        
        Gaming & Software options - 11 groups of items - 40 total selections
        
        * PC & Mac Gaming
            
        * Gaming Computers
            
        * Racing Simulators
            
        * Console Gaming
            
        * VR Gaming
            
        * Gaming Furniture
            
        * DIY Arcade Gaming
            
        * Business & Utilities
            
        * Home & Multimedia
            
        * Books & Movies
            
        * Explore All Categories

        Shop all [Gaming](https://www.microcenter.com/site/products/gaming.aspx)
        
    * Laptop Batteries
        
        Laptop Batteries options - 2 groups of items - 9 total selections
        
        * Replacement Services
            
        * Replacement Batteries

    * Clearance
        
        Clearance options - 2 groups of items - 18 total selections
        
        * Closeouts
            
        * Open Box

    * Refurbished
        
        Refurbished options - 1 groups of items - 11 total selections
        
        * Refurbished

    * Brands
        
        Brands options - 2 groups of items - 25 total selections
        
        * A - M
            
        * N - Z

    * Services
        
        Services options - 5 groups of items - 17 total selections
        
        * Troubleshooting & Repair
            
        * Custom Builds & Upgrades
            
        * Software Services
            
        * Technical Support
            
        * Service Status

    * Micro Center News
        
        Micro Center News options - 4 groups of items - 25 total selections
        
        * Micro Center News
            
        * Community Forums
            
        * Resources and Support
            
        * PC Build Showcase

    * Help
        
        Help options - 5 groups of items - 17 total selections
        
        * Help
            
        * Store Information
            
        * Your Account
            
        * Product Information
            
        * Service & Repairs

Breadcrumbs

Your privacy is important
=========================

June 5, 2024 – These updates were made to clarify our use of Google Analytics tools and to reflect that we are subject to the consumer privacy laws of an additional jurisdiction.

May 18, 2023 – The California and Other State Privacy Rights section was updated to comply with new and amended state consumer privacy laws. The “How do we handle information related to children” section was revised.

November 8, 2022 – Updated policy to include “Information from other sources”.

June 30, 2020 – The California Privacy Rights section below was updated in compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act.

This page discloses the privacy policy of Micro Electronics, Inc., Micro Center® and Micro Center Online®. We are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use.

Micro Electronics, Inc. operates retail stores and web sites under the names of Micro Center and Micro Center Online. Micro Electronics, Inc. is the parent company of these companies, and as such, when you provide information to any of these entities, this information may be combined or shared between current or future Micro Electronics, Inc. entities and subsidiaries.

This site is restricted to users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of the European Union. Users from the European Union are advised not to disclose personal information on this site.

By using this site or making purchases at our stores, you consent to this Privacy Policy. You should also review our [Safe Shopping Promise](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/security.aspx) for online purchases.

How is personally identifiable information collected?
-----------------------------------------------------

We collect and store information you provide in our stores and through our digital properties, primarily through the sales transaction and customer registration processes, but may also include other processes such as sweepstakes sign up, survey responses and email registration. We may also obtain personal and non-personal information from third-party providers.

To opt-out of any communications from Micro Center or Other Partner Companies, refer to the subscribe/unsubscribe sections below.

What personally identifiable information is collected?
------------------------------------------------------

In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business, Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), billing and shipping addresses, company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), transactional information, payment type (VISA, Check, Cash, etc.), and other information you have provided or may provide in the future, or that we have received from 3rd parties.

To enhance your Micro Center Online experience, we also collect information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (product selection, site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes). We also collect this information to create a more personalized online shopping experience and personalized marketing campaigns based on your preferences.

How is the collected information used?
--------------------------------------

Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online use your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: to process, fulfill and track online orders and in-store pickup reservations; bill your credit card for purchases; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; provide requested services such as rebate redemption and warranty coverage; offer information regarding products and services based on your interests or past purchases; hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; communicate targeted marketing/sales material via print and digital means; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you.

How do we use cookies and technology in our website?
----------------------------------------------------

Micro Center Online sets cookies on your computer to record certain information during your online visit (session). The benefit to you is the ability to save items added to your Shopping Cart and store them on our server for future reference (up to 30 days). These cookies do not gather sensitive information like your name, address, etc., if you do not specifically give that information to us voluntarily. If you have given us that information, cookies enable us to recall it (and save you the trouble of entering it all over again) each time you visit our site. Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site, and search terms entered on our site. We track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future. At your option, if you delete our cookies, you will limit our ability to personalize the site for your next visit. However, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from visiting our site and making purchases.

Google Analytics Advertising Features
-------------------------------------

Our Site uses Google Signals, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, and other Google Analytics integrated services, which are web analytics tools provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). These analytical tools use cookies, identifiers, and similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site, and to gather demographic information about our user base. These analytical tools collect information about your interaction with Micro Center including, for example, a user’s type of device or browser, the user’s IP address, the user’s browsing behavior while on the Site, the URLs of the websites that the user visited before visiting the Site, or a user’s Apple ID for advertising, and such information is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the Site, compile statistical reports on website activity, and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. We may also use the information collected to create a customer profile about a user. If you wish to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on or adjust your browser settings to disable cookies at [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We may permit service providers and third parties to collect and process some information from our digital properties. We may share personal information with those providers and other providers that engage in interest-based advertising. Our digital properties are not designed to respond to “do not track” requests from browsers.

Advertisers
-----------

We use outside advertising companies ("Advertisers") to serve advertisements on the Site. Please be advised that such Advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through use of pixel tags). If you would like more information about this practice and to learn about your choices in connection with these practices, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

You can visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) to opt out of third-party cookies.

Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information?
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

### Third party service providers:

Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online may provide your name, address and email address to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we may use such third party service providers to authorize credit card transactions, ship packages, activate gift cards and warranties, schedule and perform product installations, administer service programs, help us maintain records and analyze sales data, augment and improve the accuracy of our customer records, and distribute print and digital communications to you with our offers or important information on our behalf. None of these third party service providers are authorized to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the above stated services for which they contract with us to perform.

### Links to Third Party Sites:

Micro Center Online contains certain links and ads to third party websites, such as our vendors’ websites and links to other websites intended to facilitate our customers’ shopping experience. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these websites. We recommend that you check the privacy notice of each website you visit. Links to third party websites are provided solely for your convenience and any submission of data to such websites shall be at your sole risk.

### Information from other sources:

We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties such as the NCOA registry or other private data sources, or from you based on in-store or online transactions, that help us update, expand, and improve the accuracy of our records and your Account information. This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing.

### Other Partner Companies

We may occasionally share your name, mailing address and purchase information on a limited basis with select companies that offer products and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your information with outside partner companies, you may so indicate as noted in the unsubscribe section below.

How do I unsubscribe from Micro Center sharing my information with other companies?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* ### Unsubscribe Online
    
    It's easy. Just access our [Postal Preference Center](https://microcenterinsider.com/pub/sf/ResponseForm?_ri_=X0Gzc2X%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGlRjArpOJarq105fLDdlrvGMb0P8AJYe4nVXMtX%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGj5dbG1mfUo7izbwXNi1fgDnUwRzeb7l4toO&_ei_=EjySNquvCKNYfMgauwP6vqY) to express your preferences.
* ### Unsubscribe by Letter
    
    Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to: Communications Department, 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
    **Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
* ### Unsubscribe by Email
    
    Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com) Note: Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.

How do I subscribe to / unsubscribe from Micro Center and Micro Center Online emails or postal mailings?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

There are various methods for letting us know if you would or would not like to receive Micro Center and Micro Center Online postal or email promotions. (Please note that if you opt out of our email marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order and shipping confirmations, product recall information or other administrative communications.)

Collection of Information: We collect various information on our behalf from and about you, including information you directly provide when you use the messaging service (the “Messaging Service”). For example, we collect the phone number and/or email address you provided when signing up for the Messaging Service. When you send messages via the Messaging Service, we will also collect your messaging history and any information included in those messages. We may also collect information about you using cookies or similar technologies. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your device. Cookies enable personalization of your experience on the Messaging Service. For example, we use cookies to track the items in your Shopping Cart and may use that information to send you triggered text campaigns (e.g., sending you personalized text messages such as shopping cart reminders, browse reminders).We will not share your opt-in to an SMS campaign with any third party for purposes unrelated to providing you with the services of that campaign. We may share your data, including your SMS opt-in or consent status, with third parties that help us provide our Messaging Service, including but not limited to, platform providers and any other vendors who assist us in the delivery of text messages. **Message frequency will vary. Msg & data rates may apply, Reply STOP, Reply HELP. Reply HELP for help or email.**

For information regarding **SMS Text Messaging**, refer to our [Micro Center Insider Text Messaging terms.](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/sms-terms.aspx)

* [### Subscribe / Unsubscribe Online
    
    **For email,** visit our](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/sms-terms.aspx) [Email Preference Center](https://microcenterinsider.com/pub/sf/ResponseForm?_ri_=X0Gzc2X%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGghNPnvyI3AMpzdX7zdATq3sgwr2sYWUDaVXMtX%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGoPjl1aYUBLJiwzg1gRl4yyPfEqzbzaSfnza&_ei_=Etna52KgJplwhKMdQbhEXcU) where you can sign up to receive our various marketing promotions or request to no longer receive specified marketing promotions. All promotional emails we send you also contain a link allowing you to opt out of these specific emails in the future. Click on the relevant link and follow the simple instructions.  
    **For postal**, just access our [Postal Preference Center](https://microcenterinsider.com/pub/sf/ResponseForm?_ri_=X0Gzc2X%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGlRjArpOJarq105fLDdlrvGMb0P8AJYe4nVXMtX%3DYQpglLjHJlTQGj5dbG1mfUo7izbwXNi1fgDnUwRzeb7l4toO&_ei_=EjySNquvCKNYfMgauwP6vqY) to express your preferences.
* ### Subscribe / Unsubscribe by Letter
    
    Communications Department, 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026  
    **Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
* ### Subscribe / Unsubscribe by Email
    
    Email us at [csrs@microcenterorder.com](mailto:csrs@microcenterorder.com)  
    **Note:** Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
* ### Subscribe / Unsubscribe In-Store
    
    While visiting our retail stores, you may request to subscribe to or unsubscribe from our postal mailing lists. Please note; in order to adhere to legal guidelines involving unsubscribing from email, we cannot record your email preferences in store; this can only be accomplished through one of the other methods described above. If you opted out of receiving our postal or email marketing communications, please allow us a reasonable period of time to honor your request, as some promotions may already be in process. For email subscriptions, please allow up to a maximum of 10 business days for us to make the requested changes. Removal from our print advertising list may take up to 4 - 5 weeks, depending on the mailing cycle updating process. Of course, you always have the option to re-subscribe to our mailing lists By following the instructions listed above.

How do I make changes in the information I previously provided?
---------------------------------------------------------------

For registered users, sign in using online account name and make changes to the information you previously provided.

How do we protect the security of your Micro Center Online order information?
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Micro Electronics, Inc. and Micro Center Online are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We always use industry standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving any data that you exchange with our site. We employ the same industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that is used by major banks and stock brokerage firms to conduct business via the Internet. This encryption procedure "scrambles" the information you send us and makes online transactions extremely safe.

Sensitive information, such as financial information, will only be collected through secure web pages. Most browsers will display a green "padlock" icon indicating you are browsing on a secure page.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you via this site.

For complete details, please see our [Safe Shopping Promise](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/security.aspx).

How do we handle information related to children?
-------------------------------------------------

This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly or intentionally obtain any personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of 16. And we do not have actual knowledge about selling or sharing personal information of consumers under the age of 16. If it comes to our attention that we have unknowingly collected information from a child under the age of 16, we will take all reasonable measures to delete it as soon as possible and will not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under 16, please call us at 1-833-712-1438 or email us at custrel@microcenter.com.

California, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas and Virginia Privacy Rights
--------------------------------------------------------------------

If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Texas or Virginia, you may have certain privacy rights under state consumer privacy laws, which apply in addition to this Privacy Policy.You may learn more about those rights by clicking [here](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy-rights.aspx).

How can you contact us with questions regarding this Privacy Policy?
--------------------------------------------------------------------

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by writing to: Micro Center Online at 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026 or [calling Customer Support](https://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/contact-us.aspx). Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with your correspondence.

How am I notified of Privacy Policy changes?
--------------------------------------------

As we continue to grow our businesses and improve our services, we reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are changes or additions, we will post them. If you disagree with any of those changes or additions, you may exercise the opportunity to opt out of receiving postal and/or digital promotion from us by using the procedures described below. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at this site periodically.

This Privacy Policy is Currently in Effect.

Disclosure exceptions:
----------------------

Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website and/or Micro Center Online; to protect Micro Electronics, Inc.'s rights and property; or during emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.

In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer information, email addresses, and visitor information are generally among the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution, including, but not limited to, a bankruptcy proceeding. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is November 10, 2017.

DigiCert Authentic Site
-----------------------

Authentic Sites like microcenter.com use a DigiCert Secure Server Digital ID to offer proof of identity, to enable secure communications and to encrypt translations with site visitors through their web browser connections. The only way to be sure of a web site's authenticity is to view the site's Digital ID. Viewing a site's ID assures that you are not being "spoofed" (i.e. the site is real and not an impostor) since it contains:

* The name of the company which owns the web site (e.g. Micro Electronics, Inc.)
* The site's registered Internet address (e.g. www.microcenter.com)
* The name of the Secure Server Certification Authority under which DigiCert issued the Digital ID (RSA Data Security or DigiCert)

Sign in for the best experience
-------------------------------

Access helpful features and personalize your experience - Sign in or create an account now

Don't have an account? [Create Account](https://account.microcenter.com/auth/create?RedirectUrl=https%3a%2f%2fwww.microcenter.com%2fsite%2fcustomer-support%2fprivacy_policy.aspx)

Sign Up for Special Offers
--------------------------

As an email subscriber, you'll have **premier access** to our best offers, exclusive deals and more.

[Satisfaction Guaranteed
-----------------------

We guarantee your satisfaction on every product we sell with a full refund in accordance with our return policy – no receipt needed if you have a Micro Center Insider Account.](https://account.microcenter.com/auth/signin/)

[Service & Repair
----------------

We're your trusted local service and repair professionals.

SUPPORT & REPAIR](https://www.microcenter.com/site/service/service.aspx)

Footer Navigation
-----------------

* Customer Service
    
* Shopping
    
* Resources & Tools
    
* In-Demand & Tech

[**We're Hiring**

Work with the latest in computer and digital technology. Search the Micro Center Job Access site to review our latest Openings.

SEE CAREERS](https://www.microcenter.com/site/stores/employment.aspx)

* © 2024 Micro Electronics, Inc.

Social Media Links
